merajob.in 2015-08-10

# Privacy Policy | MeraJob.in

### Introduction

We at ‘MeraJob India Private Limited’ (hereinafter referred to as “MJI”), are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.

"Personal Information" means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, phone number and an email address or other contact information. In general, you can visit MJI's Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. MJI continues to strive to provide the safest possible environment for you to search and apply to jobs.

### Overview

  * We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to protecting information you share with us. This Privacy Policy only applies to data gathered on the MJI (the "Site"), and does not apply to any other information or web site.
  * Please review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may update it from time to time.
  * This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 1, 2013.
  * Each time you visit the Site or provide us with information, you are, by doing so, accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy at that time.
  * You (the User) agree that by using the Site you are expressly and affirmatively consenting to our use and disclosure of the information that you provide, and consenting to receive emails, as described below in this Privacy Policy.

### About Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

  * At MJI, we use cookies only for the protection and convenience of our users.
  * Cookies enable us to serve secure pages to our users without asking them to sign in repeatedly. If a user's system is idle for more than an hour, however, the cookie will expire, forcing the user to sign in again to continue their session.
  * This prevents unauthorized access to the user's information while they are away from their computer.
  * You may have the ability to reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent; however, some MJI features or services may not function properly without cookies.
  * Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed.
  * Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Site and your web experience.
  * We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.

### Third Party Services

  * Third parties provide certain services available on the Site i.e. [www.merajobindia.com](http://www.merajobindia.com/) on MJI’s behalf.
  * 'MJI' may provide information, including Personal Information, that 'MJI' collects on the Web to third-party service providers to help us deliver programs, products, information, and services. Service providers are also an important means by which 'MJI' maintains its Web site and mailing lists.
  * 'MJI' will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on MJI’s behalf.
  * 'MJI' does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on MJI’s behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against MJI’s policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent.

### Your Consent

  * By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to MJI’s processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where 'MJI' collects Personal Information on the Web.

### Information security

  * We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data on a best effort basis.
  * We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.

### Updating your information

  * We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personally identifying information for many of our services. For more information, please see the help pages for each service.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * 'MJI' does not inherently rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people on a stand-alone basis and the sharing (if any) is with relation to the general business practices of ‘MJI’ which is under your consent.

### Confidentiality and Security

  * We limit access to personal information about you to partners and employers who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with the laws prevalent in India to protect personal information about you. We seek to ensure compliance with the requirements of the Information Technology Act, 2000 and Rules made there under to ensure the protection and preservation of your privacy.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * ‘MJI’ reserves the right to update, change or modify this policy at any time. The policy shall come to effect from the date of such update, change or modification.

### Contact Information

  * ‘MJI’ welcomes your views/comments regarding this Privacy Policy at the contact address given at the Site. It is however clarified that ‘MJI’ is not obligated to comply with any requests or changes suggested by the User and MJI shall have the exclusive decision making right in this regard.
  * Should there be any concerns about infringement of this Privacy Policy, 'MJI' will employ all commercially reasonable efforts to address the same.

### Note:

  * The terms in this Privacy Policy are to be read along with the ‘Terms of Use’ (as applicable from time to time) for the Site.
  * The Terms of this Privacy Policy may be changed by MJI at any time at its sole discretion and without any obligation to inform the Users of the said changes.
  * MJI is free to offer its services to any client/prospective client without restriction
  * The Governing Law, Jurisdiction and related matters with regards this Privacy Policy shall be in accordance with the ‘Terms of Use’ of the Site.
